hey guys this is the band kneeling hip
thrust a few months ago I I posted the
uh the band standing hip thrust and I
actually like this variation more so let
me show you the setup real quick and
then I'll show you how it's done so see
on the back of the power I just have the
bands hooked up to each side and then
right here towards the front of the
power R I've got an ERX balance
pad now I'll show you the
exercise okay so from a standing
position
I'm going to squat
down position the band right in my
hips I'm going I'm going to kneel right
here on the on the a balance
pad and then from here keeping good
posture just squeeze
so first time I did this I was amazed at
how much glute activation I could get
now the way I just did it I was doing
them slow and controlled and squeezing
in but you can also just kind of pump
them out like
this but anyway as I mentioned earlier I
like this a lot more than the standing
variation I think it takes some
hamstring out of it and puts more onto
the glutes because of the bent knee
position but anyway give it a try I'm
pretty sure you're going to like it
thanks for watching